coolworks.com 2010-12-26

# Cool Works.com®- Jobs in Great Places®

## We respect your privacy

In these days of spam and online scams, we at Cool Works® are sensitive to the issues of protecting your privacy and your identity. We try to provide the safest possible environment for you to search and apply for jobs. 

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION 

Cool Works® collects personal information from users on a voluntary basis only. This allows us to give you private and secure areas for job seekers and employers to post and edit content on our site. We do not sell your personal information to anyone for any reason. When you voluntarily distribute or display personal information such as your email address or resume, others may be able to collect and use it. As a result, you may receive unsolicited messages from third parties for which Cool Works® is not responsible. 

Our sites contain links to other Web sites over which we have no control. Cool Works® is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other Web sites to which you choose to link from Cool Works®. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other Web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information. 

Please remember that if you post any of your personal information in public areas of Cool Works®, such as in online forums or chat rooms, such information may be collected and used by others over whom Cool Works® has no control. We are not responsible for the use made by third parties of information you post or otherwise make available in public areas of Cool Works®.

We use the information we gather, whether personal, demographic, collective or technical, for the purpose of operating and improving Cool Works®, fostering a positive user experience, and delivering the products and services that we offer. We may also use the information we gather to inform you of other products or services available from Cool Works® or to contact you about your opinion regarding potential new products and services that may be offered. We may use your contact information in order to send you e-mail or other communications regarding updates at Cool Works®. We have an area where you may submit feedback. Any feedback you submit becomes our property, and we can use such feedback (such as success stories) for marketing purposes or contact you for further information. 

#### ABOUT COOKIES

We use cookies at Cool Works® only for the protection and convenience of our users. Cookies enable us to serve secure pages to our users without asking them to sign in repeatedly. If a user's system is idle for more than an hour, however, the cookie will expire, forcing the user to sign in again to continue their session. This prevents unauthorized access to the user's information while they are away from their computer. 

#### JOB POSTER'S RULES 

You may not use your Document(s) to: 

  * impersonate another person, living or dead; 
  * post false, inaccurate or misleading information; 
  * post advertisements or solicitations of business 
  * post chain letters or pyramid schemes; or 
  * post opinions or notices, commercial or otherwise. 

#### JOB SEEKER RULES 

Cool Works® is under no obligation to monitor the conduct of its Users, but it may investigate and respond when violations are reported. You may not use your Document(s) to: 

  * impersonate another person, living or dead; 
  * post false, inaccurate or misleading information; 
  * post advertisements or solicitations of business 
  * post chain letters or pyramid schemes; or 
  * post opinions or notices, commercial or otherwise. 

Cool Works® makes no representations or guarantees regarding the truthfulness, accuracy, completeness, timeliness or reliability of any Documents posted by Users, or of any other form of communication engaged in by Users. 

#### WHAT YOU SHOULD KNOW 

"All users should be aware, however, that when they voluntarily display or distribute personal information (such as their email address or resume), that information can be collected and used by others. This may result in unsolicited messages from third parties for which Cool Works®is not responsible." 

YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY AND RISK FOR YOUR USE OF THE SITE, THE INTERNET GENERALLY, AND THE DOCUMENTS YOU POST OR ACCESS AND FOR YOUR CONDUCT ON AND OFF THE SITE. 

#### SOME IMPORTANT TIPS TO USE WHEN DEALING WITH PROSPECTIVE EMPLOYERS 

  * Do not give out your social security number. 
  * Never provide credit card or bank numbers on an employment application. 
  * Be cautious when dealing with contacts from other countries. 
  * Do not provide any non-work related personal information (i.e. social security number, eye color, marital status etc.) over the phone or online. 

#### OTHER PRIVACY FEATURES ON COOL WORKS

You never need to provide data to search for jobs.

Choice/Opt-Out. Cool Works® provides you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving most communications from Cool Works®. You have the option to remove your information from our database and to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. We also give you the option to change or modify the information previously provided. To exercise any of these options: 

  1. Contact us with the details of your request
  2. Send a letter to PO Box 275, Gardiner, MT 59030 
  3. Call us at 406.848.2380

#### POST A RESUME 

Posting your resume on Cool Works® puts you in front of hundreds of employers with open positions each day. When you post your resume, we automatically create a registration for you using the username and password that you supply. When you return to the site in the future you will use that same username and password to access and edit your existing resume. 

RESUME PRIVACY OPTIONS 

We know that our job seekers have varying levels of comfort when it comes to posting their resume on the Internet. To accommodate the needs of all users, Cool Works® provides different levels of privacy from which you can choose. 

  * SEARCHABLE RESUME This option gives you the most visibility to the broadest employer audience possible by making your resume searchable to our employer-clients. 
  * PRIVATE POSTING FOR APPLY ONLINE & BROADCAST ONLY This option allows you to post your resume on Cool Works® without having it searched by employers. The benefit is that you can quickly and easily apply for jobs without retyping your information AND you can elect to receive targeted jobs via broadcast email as they are posted. If you see a questionable job posting or site activity, please report the suspected fraud to us using our feedback form. If you think you have been a victim of fraud, immediately report the committed fraud to your local police and contact us using our feedback form so steps can be taken for your safety. 

#### GOOGLE ADS

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/pdfs/NAI_principles.pdf).

* * * * * * * * * * * 

Note that, by using Cool Works® Services, you signify your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use the Services. Your continued use of the Services subsequent to changes to this Policy will mean that you accept the changes.
